烟和汽油
So cigarettes and gas is...
一共79块7
$79.70
该死
Crap.
外面有取款机
Oh, there's an ATM right outside.
我不用卡的
Yeah, I don't have a card.
你也可以用身份证号写一张支票
Well, you can write a personal check with I.D.
不大方便呢
Kind of in between banks right now.
我等下来行吗
You think I could just come back later?
我肯定会回来的
I'm totally good for it. I'd come back.
我保证
I swear.
如果我能做主
If it were me, I'd be,
我会说  当然可以
"Totally, you know, no problem."
但我爸这人不好说话
But my dad is this ginormous hard---.
他在费卢杰[伊拉克城市]呆了一年
He was in Fallujah for a year,
他总是会检查收据
And he always checks the receipts.
总是会
I mean, like...always.
抱歉  我得去问他
I've got to call him. I'm sorry.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
等一下
Hold-- Hold on a second.
也许我们可以
Maybe if we could, um...
做笔交易
trade.
试过这个吗
Ever try it?
我有时会吸大麻
I mean, I smoke pot a lot sometimes.
在派对上
I party.
但这东西真会上瘾的  对吗
But-- But that stuff's really addictive, right?
其实不是  只是媒体宣传  明白吗
Not really. It's just a media thing. You know?
是什么感觉
What's it like?
棒极了
It's awesome.
让你觉得一切都非常有趣
Everything's maximum interesting.
你会有种冷冷的
You get these really cold
清爽的  像针刺一样的感觉
and sharp-like action dagger feelings.
棒极了
It's awesome.
怎么样  怎么说
Come on. What do you say?
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：灰兔灰兔     meredith49     yank121     小路
翻译：zhanginfo（老张）     时间轴：Angelica     特效：Will
■
后期：冰河       校对&监制：蛐蛐
绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第四集
感觉如何
Now, how does it feel?
疼吗
Does it hurt?
是的  很紧
Yeah, it's tight.
痛苦吗
Okay, but is it painful?
让我窒息
It's hard to breathe.
你还是得呼吸的
Well, you need your breathing.
好吧
Uh, well--
让我们搞清楚状况
Although let's not lose sight of the fact
安东尼  你是一起严重事故的受害者
That you were the victim of a terrible accident, Antonio,
有小小的不舒服是正常的
So some discomfort is to be expected.
我们就这样吧
Let's go with that one.
女士  很高兴见到你
Mucho gusto en conocerle, Senora.
下次再聊
La proxima vez,
请去结账吧
Cashier's check, por favor.
另外请把消息传出去
Oh, and spread the word.
我会就515航班提起集体诉讼
I'm building a class-action, flight 515.
原告不仅包括受害者家庭
Victims' families would be great,
还会囊括所有地面上
But I'll take anyone on he ground
受到精神创伤的人
who suffered emotionally--
比如焦虑  失眠  你能想象的
Anxiety, sleeplessness, you get the picture.
有麻烦
Trouble?
泰德·贝内克  不是吧
Ted Beneke? You cannot be serious.
就凭那个可笑的家伙
That guy is a joke.
你知道吗  沃尔特
You know what, Walt?
是你逼我这么做的
You know what? You called my bluff.
我逼你  什么意思
I called your-- What does that even mean?
你仗着我不会向警察告发你
You dared me to tell the police,
我无法这么做  你赢了
And I couldn't do it, so you win.
如果你想呆在这  没问题
If you want to stay in this house, fine,
但我们不再是夫妻
But we are not married anymore.
我跟你说过我已经不制毒了  斯凯勒
I told you that I was done cooking meth, Skyler.
我向你发过誓
Oh, right. I promised you that.
那又怎样
And so what?
起码我没有去
At least I didn't run off to go--
天啊  要知道我做的一切
Jesus! I mean, everything that I did
都是为了这个家
I did for this family.
你就自欺欺人吧
Oh, yeah, you just keep telling yourself that.
那又是什么意思
Oh, and what is that supposed to mean?
你不喜欢吗  你可以走
You don't like it? Then leave
把你那些赃钱也带走
And take your drug money with you.
这才是你的目的吧
That's what you want.
老天
Jesus.
她把钱冲掉了
Garbage disposal.
你觉得这样就能让我搬走吗
You think this will get me to move out?
你可以搞泰德
You can screw Ted.
搞屠夫  搞邮递员
You can screw the butcher, the mailman,
谁都行
Whoever you want.
你就乱搞吧
Screw them all.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
很好  那你自便吧
Good. Suit yourself.
这是好事还是坏事
Is this a good or bad thing?
你让我自便
You want me to suit myself?
我要当着他的面方便
I'll suit myself to his face!
坏事
It's a bad thing.
你好
Hello.
沃尔特·怀特要见泰德·贝内克
Walter White to see Ted Beneke.
抱歉  贝内克先生正在进行电话会议
I'm sorry. Mr. Beneke's on a conference call.
好的
Mm-hmm, okay.
我可以等
I will wait.
会有一会儿的
It could be a while.
我最不缺的就是时间
I have all the time in the world.
好的
Okay.
好  就这样吧
Here we go. Okay.
先生  贝内克先生现在没有空
Excuse me. Mr. Beneke's not available.
出来
Come on.
泰德  我看见你了
Ted, I can see you.
你就站在办公室里
I can see you standing right there in your office.
快出来
Now, come on.
快开门  我们谈谈
Open the door. Come on, let's talk.
我只是想要谈谈
I just want to talk. That's all.
像点男人样好吧
Come on, let's be men about this. Huh? Okay?
怎么样
How about that?
沃尔特  我现在正有事
Hey, Walt, I'm kind of in the middle of something right now.
是啊是啊  快开门
Oh, yes, you are. So open the door.
你就在那站着  有个屁事
You're damn right you are. You're right in the middle.
快开门  我们谈谈
Just open the door, and let's talk about it, okay?
泰德  就现在  开门
Open the door, Ted, right now.
你不想像个爷们一样解决问题是吧
All right, you don't want to be a man about it? Okay.
我还有备用计划  这个怎么样
Plan B. How do you like that? Plan B.
天啊
Oh, dear God.
我有办法
Plan B!
沃尔特  沃尔特
Walt. Walt.
沃尔特
Walt.
你在搞什么
What are you doing?
我在和泰德谈话
I'm talking with Ted.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
下次你会记得开门的
Next time, you'll open the door.
该死
Oh, damn it.
我只是来谈话的  我只是来谈话的
I'm just here to talk. I just want to talk to him.
老天  我只是想跟他谈谈都不行吗
God. Can I just talk? I just want to talk to him.
我只是想谈
I'm just talk--
好吧  好吧  我冷静了
All right. All right, all right, all right, I'm calm.
我很冷静
I'm calm.
你想干什么  你想干什么
What do you want? What do you want?
嘿  嘿  这是干什么
Hey! Hey, come on.
你到底是怎么想的
What the hell is wrong with you?
你以为你是第一个遇到这事的人吗
You act like you're the first guy this ever happened to.
我曾把我第二任妻子和我继父捉奸在床
I caught my second wife screwing my stepdad, okay?
世界本来就是残酷的  沃尔特  成熟点
It's a cruel world, Walt. Grow up.
我只想跟他谈谈
I just wanted to talk to him.
那我先跟你谈谈
Yeah, well, now I'm talking to you.
把这事当成个小插曲
Consider this an intervention.
你很有可能为此事而被捕  你懂我意思
You could have been arrested back there. You understand.
我的意思是  作为你的律师
I mean, speaking as your lawyer,
我当然很期待按小时计算薪酬
I'm always looking for billable hours,
但作为你的商业伙伴
but speaking as your business associate,
我强烈的建议你
I'm strongly advising
振作起来
that you get your shit together.
别去理那个姓贝内克的  最起码现在别
Just cool it with this Beneke guy, at least for now.
我们来谈点生意上的事
Let's talk shop
我认为这是个很好的机遇
because I think this is a great opportunity
把消极能量转化为
to channel some of that negative energy
积极能量
into something positive.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know?
什么
Sorry?
斯凯勒的事
About Skyler.
还有刚才是怎么找到我的
About where to find me just now.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know?
那完全是由于我的谨小慎微
That's just my meticulousness.
别钻牛角尖  沃尔特
Don't bog down in detail, Walt.
我的经验是
The lesson here--
你在我家装窃听器了吗
Did you bug my house?
是的  但我不确定那还是不是你家
Yeah, but I didn't know it was your house,
不是吗  你搬出去了
did I? You had moved out.
另外  也算是你让我这么做的
Besides, you basically told me to.
我让你做的
I told you to?
你曾强烈的暗示我这么做
You strongly hinted that I should.
你很担心你的妻子  还记得吗
You were worried about your wife, remember?
你很担心她会不会跟警察说些什么
You were concerned she might say something to the police.
什么  不  不  不是这样的
What? No, no, that's not true.
我什么时候说过这样的话
When the hell did I say that?
我们别在纠结谁在什么时候说了什么
Let's not get lost in the who, what, and whens.
关键在于我们尽职尽责调查了
The point is we did our due diligence,
她什么都没说
and she didn't talk.
她保持沉默了
She kept quiet.
她站在你这边  沃尔特
She stood by you, Walt,
如果你问我的话
which, if you ask me,
具讽刺意味的是还有一线希望
is the ironical silver lining here.
我的意思是  一方面
I mean, on the one hand,
当然  她背地里偷腥
sure, she snuck off the reservation
搞那些肮脏的  湿漉漉的  邪恶的事
to get some dirty, damp, and deep.
另一方面呢
On the other hand--
我炒你鱿鱼  你玩完了
You're fired! You're done!
好啊  呜呜  我不再制毒了
Good. Oh, boo-hoo, I won't cook meth anymore.
你就是个爱哭包  谁需要你啊
You're a crybaby. Who needs you?
嘿  我现在就停掉那个网址
Hey, I'm unplugging the Web site,
你觉得怎么样
How do you like that?
我现在就要你拔掉那些窃听器
I want those bugs out of my house today.
我要它们立刻拔除
I want them out now!
你刚买一套300块钱的西服  疯子
Oh, you just bought a $300 suit, psycho!
好极了  直接钻进水泥墙里
Great, drilled right into the stucco.
只是一点灰泥
Oh, a little bit of putty,
就给填上了
you'll be fine.
保证要把所有窃听器都拔了
Just make sure you get all of those things.
第一  这个小东西一个要800块钱
A, these things cost $800 apiece.
第二  你也没那么重要
B, you're not that interesting.
所以  我会把他们全都拔了的  沃尔特
So yeah, I'll get all of them, Walter.
顺便说一句  手艺不错
Great line of work, by the way.
如果用在正地方的话
Real upstanding field.
呵呵
Yep, well...
我喜欢做这事
I enjoy it.
你现在可以走了  随时
You're free to leave now. Anytime.
你知道吗  沃尔特
You know, Walter,
有时候被别人监视并不是坏事
sometimes it doesn't hurt to have someone watching your back.
怀特老师
Mr. White?
我现在有点不明白
I can't begin to understand
你到底经历了些什么  沃尔特
what you're going through, Walt,
你的健康问题
with all of your health concerns
和你所承受的压力
and the stresses you've been under.
但是  作为一名施教者
Still, as educators,
我们需要在这儿谈一谈是
there are certain responsibilities
我们对待学校和学生
we need to be meeting here
要有一定的责任心的
to the school and to the students themselves.
是的  当然
Yeah, of course.
这只是爱尔兰软毛梗吗
Is this a Wheaten terrier?
是诺福克梗
Uh, Norfolk.
诺福克梗
Norfolk?
真出人意料
That's surprising.
沃尔特  你能过来一下
Walt, could you come back over here
坐下来吗
and have a seat, please?
当然
Sure.
最近你长时间缺课
You've been absent a lot recently,
但你回到学校后
and when you are here at school,
在行为方面表现出一些问题
there have been some behavioral questions,
实话说我很担心
and frankly I'm concerned.
恩  多谢
Hm. Thank you.
你还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
你觉得我应该叫斯凯勒过来一趟吗
And do you think maybe I should call Skyler?
让我们保持这种
Let's just keep this...
什么
What?
沃尔特  你是不是有毛病
Walt, what's wrong with you?
你看  听着
You know, look,
是你一直在谈论着华盛顿的
you're the one who was talking about D.C., okay?
一路谈到这来的
This is how you get there.
你既然说了  就得接受结果
You answer the bell. You pay your dues.
另外  你知道的
Besides, it's-- you know,
被选去是件大事
it's a big deal to get picked for this.
去埃尔帕索就像参加超级碗杯
El Paso's like the Super Bowl.
我很有可能过个马路就被宰了
I could get killed crossing the street, okay?
不管怎样  我想去
Whatever. You know, I want to go.
那上次的事怎么说
What about last time?
上次怎么了
我是施拉德
Schrader.
嘿  警长
Hey, Sheriff. Yeah.
蓝的哈
Blue, huh?
事情是  恩
Thing is, uh--
我现在应该立刻上飞机的
Thing is I'm supposed to be getting on a plane right now.
那家伙拿着的是蓝色的
The stuff this guy had was blue.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
是的  我想跟他谈谈
Yeah, I want to talk to him.
出租车
Taxi.
伙计  很抱歉  我得跟你谈谈
Man, I'm sorry. I needed to talk to you,
但你不在公寓
but you weren't at your apartment.
对  我搬回家了
No, I moved back home.
这很好  不是吗
That's good, right?
是的
Yeah.
唷  你这是被开除了吗
Yo, did you just get fired?
没有  这更像是个休假吧
No. No, no, no, it's, uh... more like a sabbatical.
尚未确定  是的
Indefinite. Yeah.
最近怎么样
So what's up?
我们要先去什么地方再聊吗
Uh, should we go somewhere?
不用了  这里就挺好的
No. This is fine.
我想让你把我介绍给你的人
So, um, I want an intro to your guy.
什么人
What guy?
你的人  你的经销商
Your guy. Your distribution guy,
索尔让你们一起合作的那个人
the guy Saul hooked you up with.
不  不  杰西  别这样
No, no, no, no, no. Come on, Jesse.
我好好想过了  我想要制毒
I thought about it, and I want to.
这是我唯一擅长的事情
It's the one thing I'm good at.
不对  不是这样的
No, that is just not true.
你擅长很多事情  小子
You're good at a lot of things, son.
比如什么呢
Like what?
比如你很节制
What about your sobriety?
我跟你说过  我永远不会再吸了
I told you. I'm not using. Ever.
我就是想要重新开始做生意
I just want back into the business.
好吧  可我不想
Well, I don't.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我理解  那样很好
I know, and that's cool.
我不是想让你制毒
I'm not asking you to cook.
这是什么
What's this?
我最终就只有两个回流冷凝器了
In the end, I just went with two reflux condensers.
我也不想搞混了酸碱值
I didn't want to lose track of my Ph levels,
可是我做了你教我的所有事情
but I did everything else just like you taught me.
在数值上非常小心
Super careful in my amounts
而且在制作过程中的每一步
and watched the numbers
我都检查过数值
every step of the way.
你认为怎么样呢
So what do you think?
这很不错  对吧
It's good, right?
这里面是什么鬼东西
What in the hell is this?
什么
What?
什么  这个  就这个
What? This. This.
这是我的产品
This is my product.
这是我的配方
This is my formula.
这是我的
This is mine.
好吧  这是我们的产品
Okay, it's our product,
不过是的  我正准备让你加入我呢
but yeah, I was going to cut you in.
你想让我加入你
You were going to cut me in?
不对  不对  是我让你入伙
No, no, no. I cut you in.
你有什么毛病啊
What the hell is your problem?
我只是想让你帮我约见经销商而已
All I'm asking is for you to set a meet.
绝对不可能
Absolutely not.
为什么
Why?
因为我才不会让如此拙劣的产品
Because I am not going to lend my name
标榜上我的名号
to an inferior product.
我是说  你看看这直径
I mean, look at the diameters here.
你是用什么来进行还原反应的
What did you use for reduction?
先别说  二氧化铂  对吧
Don't tell me. Platinum dioxide, right?
不是  是汞铝合金
No. Mercury-aluminum amalgam.
二氧化铂很难保持潮湿
The dioxide's too hard to keep wet.
好吧  那你肯定哪里弄错了
All right, well, you must've done it wrong, then.
你的产品颜色都很浑浊
Your color is all cloudy,
所以你在蒸馏的时候也一定有什么问题
so you were struggling with distillation, too.
这是个非常次的次品  平克曼
Now, this is very shoddy work, Pinkman.
我都替你感到脸红
I'm actually embarrassed for you.
什么
What?
不可能  我散发了样品的
No way. I gave out samples,
每个人都说这个非常棒
and everyone said it was the bomb.
哦  他们说这非常棒哈
Oh, they said it was the bomb.
那他们是些什么人  我想知道
And who are they? I wonder.
啊  一群对冰毒上瘾的人吗
Huh? A bunch of meth heads?
-是  -是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
他们是懂的  对吗
They should know, right?
是的  好吧  对不起了
Yeah, well, sorry.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
无所谓  老顽固
Fine, ass ward.
你知道吗  我会自己去和那个人联系的
You know what? I'll contact the guy myself.
那祝你好运了  因为那人可是个专业人士
Good luck with that because my guy is a pro,
他才不会和一个吸毒的人交易
and he doesn't deal with junkies.
你知道吗  有种就来啊
You know what? Eat me.
随时  失败者  嘿  嘿
Anytime, loser. Hey. Hey!
等下  嘿
Wait. Hey!
真不敢相信这才四点而已
I can't believe it's only 4:00.
今天好漫长啊
This day is dragging.
我真想留下来
I wish I could stay.
那就留下来吧
So stay.
什么事让你没办法留下啊
What's stopping you?
什么  你是说所有的事情吗
What? Like everything, you mean?
那就说说我的疯子丈夫
How about my lunatic husband
拒绝从家里搬出去怎样
refusing to leave the house?
那就搬过来住吧
So move in here.
那样的话我儿子会更加讨厌我
And then my son hating me even more.
才不会呢
Nah.
都会过去的
That'll pass.
我经历这些事情的时候和女儿们在一起
I went through that with the girls.
她们适应的不错
They adapt.
而现在同事们都觉得
And now everyone at work thinks
我是个邪恶的想升职的婊子
I'm an evil, ladder-climbing whore.
他们都被开除了  即刻生效
They're all fired effective immediately.
还有什么
What else?
你不就是精神导师吗
Oh, aren't you the answer man.
哪里
Where did it--
你和沃尔特之间究竟出什么问题了
where did it go wrong, exactly-- you and Walt?
我是说  我看他还是挺...
I mean, I always saw him as kind of...
温柔的
mild-mannered.
是他得病后有了什么变化吗  还是
Something, I don't know, change when he got sick, or...?
我也不知道是什么变了  泰德
I don't know what changed, Ted,
我真的很不想谈论这个事情
and I just don't feel really comfortable talking about it.
抱歉
Sorry.
就是出于私心才问的
Just asking out of self-interest.
想要确保我不会犯同一个错误
Got to make sure I don't make the same mistake.
会的话我会很惊讶的
I would be amazed.
看看我是不是理解对了  拉塞尔
Just let me see if I'm following you here, Russell.
你从Gasparza里的一个穿着棕黄色裤子的人
You got this stuff from some guy at Gasparza's
手里得到了这个东西
who was wearing tan pants
你有80%的信心肯定他是有胡子的
and who you're 80% sure had a mustache.
就这样  对吗
That's it, right?
这就是你的大脑尽全力工作的结果了吗
That's your brain working at maximum capacity?
拉塞尔
Russell.
没事吧
Everything all right in there?
梅尔  那小子叫梅尔
Mel. The dude's name was Mel.
好啊  这就对了  看到了吗
Well, there you go. See?
你还是有些用处的
You served an actual earthly function.
真不敢相信我还记得那个
I can't believe I remembered that.
叫梅尔什么
Mel who?
记得他姓什么吗
Does he have a last name?
是的  梅尔
Yeah, uh, Mel.
等下
Wait.
是梅尔么
Was it Mel?
恩  叫马克吧
Um...Mark.
肯定是以个"M"开头的一个名字
It was definitely an "M" Name.
天哪  我就要忘掉了
Oh, man, I'm losing it.
等等  等等
Wait, wait.
是的
Yeah.
我忘掉了
It's gone.
忘掉了
不过是个以"M"开头的名字
It was an "M" name, though.
我记得那是个"麽"的发音
I remember the "Muh" Sound.
哦  啊
Oh. Huh?
我们就找名字开头发"麽"音的
We'll go with the "Muh" sound.
多谢
Thanks a lot.
谢谢
Yeah.
他穿的肯定是黄褐色裤子
He definitely had tan pants.
我想阉了自己
Remind me to get a vasectomy.
好  现在9点多
Okay, it's after 9,
乔治女孩驻唱的那家酒吧
so this bar that Girl George is at,
这时大概遍地人渣了
probably wall-to-wall dirtbags by now.
咱去瞧瞧热闹
Let's go have a little looky-loo,
看能不能找到那M打头的家伙
see if we can't find this M-named clown.
怎么了
What?
这是条线索
It's a lead.
什么线索
Lead to what?
能找到海森堡的线索
To Heisenberg.
早和你说过就是个时间问题
I told you it was only a matter of time
这家伙肯定憋不住的
before this guy booted up again.
走吧  伙计
Here we go, my friend.
格米  别怨我运气好
Don't hate me because I'm beautiful, Gomie.
道个歉再请我喝一杯  就完事了
Just apologize and buy me a beer.
老兄  你太过了
Man, you're reaching.
那玩意可能是别人做的
This stuff could be a knockoff
或者是那老家伙剩下的
or left over from an older cook.
你凭什么就认为海森堡又重现江湖了
How do you know Heisenberg's gearing up again?
凭什么
How do I know?
因为我就是知道
Because I know.
反正我不信
I don't get it.
你就为这把任务小组派出去的么
This is the reason why you're blowing off the task force?
就为查那几个臭小子
Chase down teeners?
最讨厌你们这些马后炮了
I'm getting tired of all the second guessing.
你要觉得这次调查缺少刺激的话
If you're not sufficiently stimulated by this investigation,
行行好  快调走得了
do us both a favor and ask for a transfer.
你最近什么毛病
What is up with you lately?
在酒吧打架
Starting bar fights?
拒绝去埃尔帕索
Turning down El Paso?
现在又是这些屁话
And now this bullshit?
我看你需要找人谈谈了
Do you need to talk to someone or what?
找人谈
Talk to someone?
找谁
Talk to who?
伙计  我不想触怒你
I'm not trying to step on your toes, bro. Okay?
我是为你担心  没其它的
I'm just worried about you. That's all.
领教了  "伙计"
Appreciate that...bro.
现在把你手从我身上拿开
Now take your hand off my shoulder.
我就是电视上那个人
Yeah, yeah, the one that was on TV.
有什么小零碎儿掉在你家吗
Did any little piece fall on your property?
林卡斯先生  我不是找整个的机翼
I'm not looking for an entire wing here, Mr. Linkas.
也许就是个螺丝或者螺帽
It could be a nut or a bolt.
还可能是点极小的玩意
It could be a bag of peanuts,
只要这空难还让继续你纠结的话
just so long as it caused you pain and suffering.
别进来  把门关上
Oh, no, no, no. Closed.
我回头打给你
Uh, calling you back.
机会已经给你了
You had your chance.
跟你说要让他接着搞
I told you to get him cooking again,
可你却搞砸了  现在晚了
and you blew it off, and now it's too late.
那家伙现在冲我们大发神经
The guy's gone mass maniac on us!
本来我是想让你们爷俩发光发热
All I wanted was to show you two your potential,
可我现在又得到了个屁
and what do I get in return?
反而是骨折  瞧瞧我这伤
A bone contusion. You want to see the scar?
就希望你俩...
I wish you two had--
这个...
Hi, there.
你是你怎么让沃尔特...
How in the hell did you get Walt to--
我自己搞出来的
I made it.
你以为只有他能做
You know the guy who knows the guy, right?
好消息是对于一个晚期癌症患者来说
Uh, good news is, for a stage three cancer,
他事情做得的确不错
the guy's doing well physically.
精神上却...
Mentally,
彻底失败
the guy's a disaster.
他跟他老婆坦诚了这事
He's gone off the rails over this thing with his wife.
我看他不会再干了
My opinion, he's not coming back,
反正自己是不干了
not on his own.
还有  你那些朋友又找他去了
Your friends were at his place again, by the way.
在他家外面的路上画上了些东西
They drew something on the street outside his house.
大镰刀
The scythe.
这帮畜生
Animals.
-律师知道了吗  -该让他知道吗
- Does the lawyer know? - Should he?
不
No.
你要还想让他再制毒的话
If you want this guy to produce again,
干嘛不跟他说呢
why not just tell him?
你是唯一一个多少还在维护他的人
You're the only thing that stands between him and an ax in the head.
恐惧可不是有效的动力
I don't believe fear to be an effective motivator.
我要他全身心投入
I want investment.
我眼下只对他能活多久感兴趣
For now, I'm simply interested in time frame.
他不会死的太快吧
He will live for the foreseeable future, yes?
没错
Mm, foreseeable,
至少有几年吧
couple years at least,
不考虑天灾人祸的话
barring acts of God and men with axes.
律师告诉我
Oh, from the lawyer,
应该让你知道
I'm supposed to let you know
平克曼小子正找机会出手呢
the Pinkman kid is looking to sell.
我不跟嗑药的搅在一起
I don't work with junkies.
想你也会这么说
That's what I thought you'd say.
可能这样最稳妥
Probably for the best.
听说他和沃尔特单飞了
What I hear, he and Walter are splitsville.
有这事
Really?
古德曼说的
That's what Goodman says.
谁知道呢
Cats and dogs.
按计划办吧
Do the deal.
您有一条未接留言
You have one unheard message.
施拉德探员
Agent Schrader,
尽快给我回电
you need to be calling me back ASAP.
我感觉整个德州都在盯着我  我就没...
I've got Texas breathing down my neck, and I'm not about--
马特上周被炒后就没见过
Yeah, I haven't see Matt since he got fired last week.
你看我该去哪儿找他
Where can I find him, you think?
不知道   我没见过他...
No idea. I haven't seen him--
行了  你都说好几遍了
I know. You said that a few times.
可我就是没见过他啊
Yeah, because I haven't seen him.
我不知道还能说什么
I don't know what else to say.
亲爱的  你叫什么
What's your name, darling?
卡拉
Cara.
卡拉  这玩意从哪儿来的
Where did this come from, Cara?
我...我不知道
I-- I don't know.
这是...毒品吗
What is it? Drugs?
听着  我刚才就想说了
Look, I'm just going to come right out and say it.
卡拉  你骗人还嫩点
Um, you're a bad liar, Cara.
别跟我扯
Don't get me wrong.
比这糟糕的我见多了
Not the worst I've ever seen.
有次抓到一个肛门藏着毒囊的家伙
Once had a guy try to explain the dope balloon up his butt
楞说那是什么泰餐
on bad Thai food.
所以你骗人还真不行
Still, you're not a very good liar.
我真的不知道
I honestly don't know
够了
Stop.
你看着像个好姑娘
You look like a good kid.
我到这不是找你麻烦的
I'm not here to get you in trouble,
不过你得赶紧告我这东西从哪儿来
but you need to tell me where this came from right now!
我发誓从没做过这东西
I never do stuff like this. I swear to God.
我尝过点  难受死了  所以就给了马特
I tried it, and I hated it, so I just gave it to Matt.
谁给你的
Okay, and who gave it to you?
有个人几天前来的
Some guy, he came in a couple days ago
拿这个跟我换过汽油
and wanted to trade it for gas.
有个人  叫什么
Some guy? W-What's his name?
算了
Okay, w--
他长什么样儿
What did he look like?
我不知道  不过...
I don't know. Um--
大众脸
He looked pretty normal.
白种人
You know? Um, white--
我记得他的头发有点淡棕色
I think his hair was lightish brown.
眼睛很蓝
He had really blue eyes.
碧蓝碧蓝的那种
They were really, really blue.
他很迷人  还有呢
He's dreamy. Okay, w-w-what else?
身上是否有刺青  佩戴何首饰
Piercings,jewelry,
着装风格呢
distinctive articles of clothing?
好好想想
Come on.
快想想
听我说
Listen to me.
找到这个贩毒男
It's real important
真的很重要
that I find the person that had these drugs,
你能否回忆起其他细节
so if you can remember anything else about him...
好好想想
Come on.
快想想
快点想
Come on.
他开一辆旅行房车
He drove an RV.
很好  很好
Okay, good, good.
还记得什么  车型怎样
What can you remember? What kind of RV?
何种颜色  看到过车牌吗
What color? Did you spot a license plate?
我不知道车型
I don't know the kinds,
也没看到车牌
and I didn't see the license,
但颜色  我记得是白褐相间
but the color was, I think, white, brownish color.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道没能帮到你
I know I'm not helping you, but...
请别告诉我爸爸
Please don't tell my dad.
卡拉
Cara.
这摄像头还在运作吧
Please tell me that that camera works.
该死
Damn it.
有了
Bingo.
这些蛋煎得不错  妈妈
These eggs are good, Mom.
谢谢
Thanks.
最近有点奇怪
Hey, you know what's weird?
老爸的筹款网站
Dad's Web site.
自最后一次捐赠后  已经有三天没动静了
It's been three days since the last donation.
是啊  好吧
Yeah, well...
大家都没兴趣了
people lose interest.
你打算休息多久
So how long are you off for?
几个星期
A few weeks.
视情况而定吧
Uh, we'll play it by ear.
我可能太急进了点
I probably... pushed it, you know,
这么快就重返岗位了
going back to work so soon.
那我今天能搭个车吗
Think-- Think I can get a ride today?
路易斯去看医生了
Louis has a doctor's appointment.
可以
Uh...yeah.
那么爸爸可以照看妹妹了  对吧
Hey, so dad can babysit now. Right?
你不会想天天都把霍莉带去公司吧
You won't have to take Holly to work every day.
总会有机会
Sometime, maybe.
看看再说
We'll see.
怎么样
What's up?
我想你会飘飘欲仙的  唷
I think you'll seriously enjoy, yo.
等等
Wait.
不对不对
No, no.
不对  等等
No. Wait.
喂
Hey!
Hey.
搞什么  这里才一半
What the hell? This is only half.
对极了  给你的那一半
That's right. It's your half.
唷
Yo!
贱人  另一半呢
Where's the other half, bitch?
这真有点
I mean, it was, uh-- --
这一切都太不可思议了  伙计
The whole thing was crazy, man.
可怜的家伙  为他深感遗憾
Poor bastard. I felt sorry for him.
他还以为我们是王牌特派员呢
He actually thought we were the cable guys, you know?
总之
Anyway, uh, um,
很抱歉对你的不敬  长官
sorry about those miscalls, Chief.
我已经换了线人  这事不会再发生了
I'm changing providers. It won't happen again.
你打算去埃尔帕索吗  汉克
Are you going to El Paso, Hank?
是啊
Hell, yes!
脚蹬尖头皮靴  帅气十足
With pointed boots and bells on.
但我得先破了海森堡这个案子
Just I got this break in the Heisenberg case.
你是说  那个蓝色冰毒案
The blue meth, you mean?
就凭小孩身上的那货
The teenth?
当然  就是这小孩带来了转机
Yeah, well, that teenth got things rolling.
我一直追踪到了锡沃拉的一家加油站
I traced it to a gas station in Cibola.
在那儿弄到这些线索
That's where I got these.
加油站的监视器被关了
Now, the station's, uh, closed circuit, uh, was down--
惊喜  惊喜
surprise, surprise--
但我从自动取款机的监视摄像中
but I was able to pull some of these snapshots
拿到了这些快照
off an ATM security camera.
我一直都怀疑
Hey, now, I always thought
这些家伙是在野外制毒  对吗
these guys might be camper cooking, right?
首先  这种含内饰的
First off, your typical Class C motor home
C类旅行房车
is going to grunt at least 5,000 pounds
至少得5000英镑
of interior fixtures, okay?
内饰包括家电  家具  内置器具
We're talking appliances, furniture, built-ins.
起码5000英镑  对吧
5,000 pounds at least, okay?
看到这车的速度多快了吧
See how high that suspension's riding?
要是负载那么多内饰是不可能达到这种速度
No way, no how, this thing's carrying that kind of weight.
显然是被去除了内饰
I mean, this thing has been cleared out
以提高密封度
and stripped down to its tight and curlies.
其用途是什么呢
For what?
用来做血库
Blood bank?
还是流动书库
Maybe a bookmobile?
没有车牌的清晰截图
There's no clear view of the plates.
是啊  差点运气  是吧
Yeah, well, you can only get so lucky, right?
事实上这车子并没有前车牌
But the fact that there's no front plate
更像是在新墨西哥州登记注册
tells me its likely New Mexico registration.
我去车管所确认过
I checked with DMV.
该州注册在案的这种80年代巴士
There are only 29 of these early '80s Bounders
只有29辆
registered in the state.
Only 29?
正是
Yeah.
所以只需进行探访即可
So I got to go, uh, you know, knock on some doors.
汉克  你得去埃尔帕索上任
They need you in El Paso, Hank.
没问题
You bet. I-- I--
我得先破了海森堡一案
I'm just going to wrap up this Heisenberg thing first.
言下之意  你是拒绝上任喽
So you're refusing the assignment.
我没这意思  我会去的
No, I'm not. I'll go.
得再过段时间
It's just I need some more time.
你根本没听我讲话  施拉德探员
You're not hearing me, Agent Schrader.
时间所剩无几
You're out of time.
你今晚是否去埃尔帕索上任
Are you going to El Paso now? Tonight?
只要回答去或者不去
Just a simple yes or no.
不去
No.
我去不了
I can't.
但那是因为
But that's only because
我马上就能破获大案了
I'm really close to something big here.
那就给我立马破案
Better get to it, then.
正在播出的是KECA480  阿尔布开克广播新闻
This is KECA 480, Albuquerque news radio.
KECA新闻10点13
KECA news time 10:13.
今天的头条新闻是
Our top story this hour--
唐纳德·马格里斯  空中交通管制员
Donald Margolis, the air traffic controller
他因为造成了最近的空难  致使167人丧生
criticized for his role in the recent air disaster
而备受指责
in which 167 persons died,
于今早被送往地方医院
was rushed to an area hospital early this morning,
显然
apparently the victim
他曾试图举枪自尽
of a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
对此警察未发表任何声明
Police won't say whether or not--
你的那份
Your half.
马上开  马上开
Okay, okay.